Guide to the Dan Nimrod papers, 1938-2002 MS2192
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Correspondence - United States, 1956-2002; MS2192 Series 5; 10.5 Linear feet
  - Centre for Global Security Inc. - Pritikin, Roland (Brig Gen) Misc. Documents, 1956-1993 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Centre for Holocaust Studies, 03/27/1980-04/21/1985 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Centre for Near-East Policy Research - Soloway, Arnold (prof), 03/19/1984-09/1994 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Christian Copts of California, 08/23/1992-10/15/1992 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Christian Mid-East Conference - Mazar, Ori N. (dr), 04/14/1989-04/27/1990 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Chronicles of Culture - Persuasion at Work - the Rockford Papers of the Rockford Institute, 06/15/1981-09/29/1989 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Cinis, Philip H., 05/30/1980-11/10/1980 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Coalition for Israel, 08/30/1993-09/10/1993 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Coalition for Jewish Concerns (A.M.C.H.A.) - Weiss, Avi (rabbi), 12/05/1994-01/24/1995 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Cohen, Melvin - Golden Rule Society, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Cohen, William, 05/17/1978-07/12/1979 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Committee for accuracy in Middle East Reporting in America (C.A.M.E.R.A.), 06/21/1990-11/24/1999 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Committee of Jewish Idea - Drissman, Michael, 04/07/1980-01/18/1999 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Congregation Shaar Hashamayin - Kasten, Elihu (Rabbi Dr), 04/21/1980-08/14/1995 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Congregation Sha'arai Shomayin - Jacobs, Steven J (rabbi), 02/12/1978-06/16/1978 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Congregations, 05/03/1978-10/05/1981 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    [from contents page of folder:] Agudas Achim - Herring, Bill (rabbi); Beth Yeshurum - Segal, Jack; B'nai Israel; Monmouth Reform Temple; Rabbinical Assembly; Rose (rabbi); Temple Rodeph Shalom; United Synagogues of Greater Hartford
  - Consulate General of Israel, 12/16/1985 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Cornfield, Giveon (dr), 10/28/1992-12/02/1993 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Cramer, Laurence 1978, 03/10/1978-11/20/1978 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Cramer, Laurence 1979, 01/03/1979-12/28/1979 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Cramer, Laurence 1980[-1983], 01/04/1980-01/04/1983 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Cuban American National Foundation - Calzon, Frank, 05/16/1984-04/09/1985 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Dallen, Michael C. Esq., 03/07/1988-09/14/1989 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Dee, Rachel H., 08/05/1979-06/20/1986 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - DeKovner-Mayer, Barbara, 01/30/1981-07/26/1990 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Deligdish, Joseph, 02/22/1979-01/26/2001 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Dolphin, Lambert (dr), 05/21/1987-07/06/1987 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Dworkin, Bud, 10/19/1982-06/06/1989 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dyen, Samuel 1978-1979, 05/15/1978-12/28/1979 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Dyen, Samuel 1980-1981, 01/10/1980-12/31/1981 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Dyen, Samuel 1982-1985, 01/20/1982-12/16/1985 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Dyen, Samuel 1986-1987, 03/31/1986-12/29/1987 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Dyen, Samuel 1988-1997, 03/14/1988-12/21/1997 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Dyen, Samuel 1998-2001, 08/20/1998-03/01/2001 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Embassy of Israel, 01/07/1979-05/01/1984 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Eretz Yisrael Movement, 03/1985-11/12/1986 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Facts & Logic about the Middle East (F.L.A.M.E.) - Joffe, G., 08/16/1993-09/13/2001 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Faulk, Gilbert (Accountant), 05/23/1978-11/11/1981 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Felgar, Robert, 03/30/1997-04/13/2002 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Finkel, Mitchell W., 06/12/1981-01/24/1990 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Flansberg, Gerald, 10/28/1985-08/18/2000 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - FOCUS - Flacks, Paul, 04/29/1986-12/27/1995 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Fox, Tamar, 09/05/1980-01/20/1981 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Frank, Arthur, 04/04/1985-05/05/1985 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Freeman Center for Strategic Studies - Maccabean - Shapiro, Bernard J. (Director) 1993, 01/22/1993-12/15/1993 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Freeman Centre for Strategic Studies - Maccabean - Shapiro, Bernard J. (Director) 1994-1995, 02/13/1994-12/14/1995 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Freeman Centre for Strategic Studies - Maccabean - Shapiro, Bernard J. (Director) 1996-2000, 06/20/1996-04/17/2000 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Freeman Centre for Strategic Studies - Maccabean - Shapiro, Bernard J. (Director) Misc. Documents, 02/18/1993-02/25/1996 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Freyer, Carl, 01/13/1995-10/04/2000 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Friedman, Barry (ass't prof Valdosta State College), 06/06/1978-03/12/1989 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe 1978-Jun 1986, 10/14/1978-06/30/1986 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe Jul-Dec 1986, 07/21/1986-12/25/1986 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe Jan-Mar 1987, 01/04/1987-03/27/1987 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe Apr-Jun 1987, 04/03/1987-06/13/1987 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe Jul-Sep 1987, 07/08/1987-09/29/1987 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc - Spen, Monroe Oct-Dec 1987, 10/01/1987-12/31/1987 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc - Spen, Monroe Jan-Mar 1988, 01/05/1988-04/09/1988 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc - Spen, Monroe Apr-May 1988, 04/05/1988-06/18/1988 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe Jun 1988, 06/01/1988-06/28/1988 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe Jul-Aug 1988, 07/05/1988-08/31/1988 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe Sep-Oct 1988, 09/01/1988-11/07/1988 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe Nov-Dec 1988, 11/01/1988-12/30/1988 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe Jan-Feb 1989, 01/03/1989-02/28/1989 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe Mar-May 1989, 03/05/1989-05/24/1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe Jun-Dec 1989, 06/02/1989-10/04/1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe 1990-1991, 01/02/1990-11/07/1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe 1992-1994, 02/07/1992-10/25/1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Friends of Jerusalem Temple Mount Inc. - Spen, Monroe 1995-1997, 01/31/1995-03/04/1997 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - George Washington University 1999, 01/14/1999-12/13/1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - George Washington University 2000-2001, 01/14/2000-09/14/2001 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Ginsberg, Nettie, 01/18/1981-12/27/1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Ginzburg, Emmanuel, 06/20/1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Givner, Solomon, 03/20/1981-06/27/1985 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Goldstein, Sanford, 06/26/1985-07/08/1985 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Greenberg, Jacob L., 09/14/1993-12/24/2000 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Greenfield, Richard - The Greenfield Collection of Selected Articles, 10/26/1990-08/15/1997 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Grissom, Roy Neal, 07/26/1982-05/02/1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Gush Emunim, 09/10/1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Harvard University - Widener Library, 05/08/2000-06/01/2000 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Hatikva - Zacharowicz, Leon, 02/13/1984-02/18/1985 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Hebrew Theological College, 02/1984-04/30/1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Hebrew Union College, 11/28/1977-06/22/1982 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Hebron, Jewish Community of, 09/05/1992-07/13/1995 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Heilweil Family, 11/29/1990-02/18/1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Heller, Kenneth, 08/27/1978-12/28/1979 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Herut-Hatzohar - Zionist Revisionists Likud USA Inc., 10/05/1977-1995 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Holocaust Museum Philadelphia - Rosen, Philip (dr), 06/24/1994-09/12/1994 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Holocaust Studies (centre for), 03/27/1980-11/19/1985 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. 1974-1983, 06/1974-12/06/1983 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq., 01/04/1984-12/28/1984 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Feb-Jun 1985, 01/10/1985-06/27/1985 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jul-Dec 1985, 07/01/1985-12/30/1985 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. 1986-Aug 1987, 01/13/1986-08/31/1987 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Sept 1987, 09/01/1987-09/28/1987 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Oct-Dec 1987, 10/02/1987-12/29/1987 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jan-Apr 1988, 01/03/1988-04/29/1988 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. May 1988, 05/02/1988-05/31/1988 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jun-Jul 1988, 06/02/1988-07/29/1988 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Aug-Sep 1988, 08/08/1988-09/30/1988 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Oct-Nov 1988, 10/03/1988-11/30/1988 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Dec 1988, 12/02/1988-12/30/1988 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jan 1-15, 1989, 01/03/1989-01/13/1989 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jan 16-31, 1989, 01/16/1989-01/31/1989 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Feb 1989, 02/01/1989-02/28/1989 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Mar 1-15 1989, 03/01/1989-03/15/1989 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Mar 16-31, 1989, 03/16/1989-03/31/1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Apr 1-18, 1989, 04/01/1989-04/18/1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Apr 19-30, 1989, 04/19/1989-04/30/1989 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. May 1-10 1989, 05/01/1989-05/10/1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. May 11-20, 1989, 05/11/1989-05/20/1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. May 21-31, 1989, 05/21/1989-05/31/1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq Jun 1-10, 1989, 06/01/1989-06/10/1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jun 11-21, 1989, 06/11/1989-06/21/1989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jun 21-30, 1989, 06/21/1989-06/30/1989 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jul 1-10, 1989, 07/01/1989-07/10/1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jul 11-20, 1989, 07/11/1989-07/20/1989 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jul 21-31, 1989, 07/21/1989-07/31/1989 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Aug 1-15, 1989, 08/01/1989-08/15/1989 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Aug 16-31, 1989, 08/16/1989-08/31/1989 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Sep 1-14, 1989, 09/03/1989-09/14/1989 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Sept 15-30, 1989, 09/15/1989-09/30/1989 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Oct 1-15, 1989, 10/02/1989-10/13/1989 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Oct 16-31, 1989, 10/16/1989-10/31/1989 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Nov-Dec 1989, 11/01/1989-12/29/1989 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jan 1990, 01/02/1990-01/30/1990 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Feb 1990, 02/01/1990-02/28/1990 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Mar 1990, 03/01/1990-03/30/1990 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Apr 1990, 04/02/1990-04/30/1990 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. May 1990, 05/01/1990-05/31/1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jun 1990, 06/03/1990-06/29/1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jul-Aug 1990, 07/05/1990-08/29/1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Sep 1990, 09/01/1990-09/28/1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Oct 1990, 10/01/1990-10/31/1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Nov 1990, 11/01/1990-11/30/1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Dec 1990, 12/03/1990-12/31/1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jan 1991, 01/06/1991-01/31/1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Feb 1991, 02/01/1991-02/28/1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Mar 1991, 03/04/1991-03/29/1991 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. April 1991, 04/01/1991-04/30/1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. May-Jun 1991, 05/01/1991-06/27/1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jul 1991, 07/02/1991-07/31/1991 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Aug 1991, 08/01/1991-08/30/1991 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Sep 1991, 09/03/1991-09/30/1991 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Oct-Nov 1991, 10/01/1991-11/27/1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Dec 1991, 12/02/1991-12/26/1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jan-Mar 1992, 01/01/1992-03/30/1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Apr-Sep 1992, 04/06/1992-09/30/1992 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Oct-Dec 1992, 10/05/1992-12/30/1992 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jan-Apr 1993, 01/01/1993-04/22/1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. May-Sept 1993, 05/03/1993-09/29/1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Oct-Dec 1993, 10/04/1993-12/28/1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jan-Apr 1994, 01/03/1994-04/28/1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. May-Sep 1994, 05/04/1994-09/29/1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Oct-Dec 1994, 10/05/1994-12/29/1994 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jan-Jun 1995, 01/16/1995-06/29/1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jul-Dec 1995, 07/03/1995-12/26/1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jan-Mar 1996, 01/01/1996-03/27/1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Apr-Dec 1996, 04/02/1996-12/24/1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jan-May 1997, 01/02/1997-05/27/1997 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jun-Dec 1997, 06/02/1997-12/22/1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jan-May 1998, 01/22/1998-05/22/1998 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jun-Dec 1998, 06/03/1998-12/16/1998 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. 1999, 01/06/1999-12/16/1999 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Horwin, Leonard esq. Jan-Jun 2000, 01/07/2000-07/29/2000 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Hultmark, Sarah, 08/14/1983-03/04/1985 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Huttenbach, Henri (prof), 02/14/1984-10/16/1984 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Insights books and research service - Gilman, R., 04/11/1977-08/05/1982 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Institute of Hebrew Unity - Margulis, Aaron, 01/14/1978-07/08/1980 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Institute for Mediterranean Affairs - Merlin, Samuel, 08/09/1979-10/15/1985 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - International Christian Embassy - Jerusalem, 07/11/1992 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - International Conference for PEACE (Preventing the Emergence of Another Arab Country in Judea, Samaria, and Gaza), 01/1980-11/21/1980 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - International League for the Repatriation of Russian Jews Inc. - Brafman, Morris, 12/22/1978-07/09/1980 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - International Rabbinic Committee for the Safety of Israel, 05/04/1981-05/04/1982 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - International Security Council CAUSA International, 06/22/1984-08/29/1988 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Isaac, Rael Jean (dr), 01/01/1980-05/12/2000 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Islamic Propaganda [El-Yacoubi, H. & J. (drs)], 04/19/1991 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    This folder contains a letter from Drs. H. & J. El-Yacoubi to Nimrod, suggesting he order their book. The folder label is Nimrod's.
  - Israel News Bulletin - Medoff, Rafael (prof - Columbus University - Ohio), 12/17/1980-06/13/1994 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Israel Today - The Female Connection - Dekovner-Mayer, Barbara, 03/31/1980-07/26/1990 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Israeli & Global News - Kahl, Murray, 03/09/1994-03/21/1996 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Jaffe, Herbert (prof), 12/11/1990-07/25/1995 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Jewish Book Council, the, 07/24/1980-12/01/1980 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Jewish Combatants - Kowalski, Isaac, 03/12/1981-10/30/1981 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Jewish Community Centre of Greater Phoenix - Jolovitz, Meir, 05/01/1979-12/09/1980 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Jewish Defense League (J.D.L.), 07/30/1979-09/06/1999 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Jewish Digest, 02/26/1981-12/02/1981 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Jewish Heroes and Martyrs of the 20th Century - Israel's Stamp Collectors Society (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Jewish Idea - Conference of Jewish Activists - Drissman, Michael (prof Macomb Community College), 04/07/1980-09/15/2000 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Jewish Observer, 07/08/1985-08/25/1985 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Jewish Political Caucus & Jewish Political Chronicle, 06/17/1985-08/23/2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Press, 03/27/1978-04/13/2001 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Right, the - 1981-1984 Eisenberg, David & Gabor, Georgia, 08/19/1981-11/16/1984 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Right, the - 1985-1986 Eisenberg, David & Gabor, Georgia M., 04/22/1985-02/25/1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Speakers Bureau - Small, Paul, 07/02/1978-02/10/1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Unity Movement (Seattle) - Joselow, Ken & Jane (Alias Ben Shimon), 01/03/1984-04/04/1989 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Week, 08/01/1979-08/28/2000 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Jordan is Arab Palestine (J.I.P.), 08/27/1981-01/18/1985 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Joshua Circle - Baldwin, Sidney (California State University in Fullerton), 09/09/1980-01/11/1990 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Kach International, 05/02/1985-08/23/1991 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Katz, Sharon, 04/03/1983-05/01/1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Kaufman, Jerome S. (D.O., F.A.C.O.), 04/01/1996-05/31/2001 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Kesselman Foundation, 10/27/1989-06/10/1990 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Kiraly, Bella K. (prof Brooklyn College), 09/09/1980-03/08/1983 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Kranz, Herzl (rabbi), 02/09/1981-08/17/1987 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Lang Fan, Mark E. esq., 10/30/1992-11/19/1992 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Larchmont Temple - Poller, Leonard (rabbi), 10/31/1977-09/23/1986 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Latz, Arje (phd), 12/07/1988-04/07/1989 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Lehmann, Manfred (dr), 01/12/1997-01/21/1997 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Lerner, Paula, 02/10/1986-04/17/1986 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Levine, Hillel (phd, prof), 11/06/1998-02/11/1999 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Library of Congress, 12/17/1978-08/22/1990 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Life in Israel - The Times of Israel - Epstein, A.S. 1978-Mar 1980, 05/25/1978-02/19/1980 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Life in Israel - The Times of Israel - Epstein, A.S. Jun-Dec 1980, 06/13/1980-12/10/1980 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Life in Israel - The Times of Israel - Epstein, A.S. 1981-1982, 01/29/1981-12/02/1982 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Life in Israel - The Times of Israel - Epstein, A.S. 1983, 01/10/1983-12/12/1983 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Life in Israel - The Times of Israel - Epstein, A.S. 1984, 01/14/1984-10/20/1984 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Life in Israel - The Times of Israel - Epstein, A.S. 1985-1989, 02/12/1985-11/18/1989 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Life in Israel - The Times of Israel - Epstein, A.S. 1990-1992, 01/02/1990-12/24/1992 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Life in Israel - The Times of Israel - Epstein, A.S. Misc. Documents (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Likud, friends of - The Jerusalem Insider, 08/11/1992-05/26/1997 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Lively Communications Inc. - Lively, Scott, 05/02/1996-10/01/1998 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Loewenberg, Robert (prof), 04/04/1979-06/03/1986 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Magen David Adom - Operation Recognition - Dobin, Rubin (rabbi), 05/22/1978-12/21/1981 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - MAPAM - United Workers Party - Haviva, Givat, 01/10/1988 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Markus, Hadassa, 09/14/1980-03/14/1988 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Maurer, Marvin (prof - Monmouth College), 04/20/1984-12/16/1985 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Media - General, 1970-2000 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    [from contents page of folder:] Commentary; Imprimis; Near North News; New York Post; New York Times; Newsweek; South West Times Record; TIME
  - Media - Jewish - Misc., 1978-2000 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    [from contents page of folder:] American Jewish Ledger; American Jewish Life; American Zionist; B'nai B'rith Messenger; Book News Inc.; Israel Radio; Israel Shelanu; Jewish Herald Voice; Jewish Press; Jewish Veteran; Jewish Voice & Opinion; Jewish Week; Martyrdom & Resistance; Southern Israelite
  - Middle East Review - Curtis, Michael (dr) (Rutgers State University of New Jersey), 05/01/1986-03/16/1987 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Midstream - Carmichael, Joel, 08/06/1979-02/24/2001 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Miller, Martin 1981-1987, 05/03/1981-11/18/1987 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Miller, Martin 1988-2002, 01/03/1988-03/21/2002 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Modell, Sol (prof - Valley College) 1981-1983, 03/11/1981-11/08/1983 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    For more of Modell's writings, see Series 11.
  - Modell, Sol (prof - Valley College) 1984-1985, 01/10/1984-12/18/1985 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Modell, Sol (prof - Valley College) 1986-1987, 01/23/1986-12/29/1987 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Modell, Sol (prof - Valley College) 1988, 01/14/1988-12/08/1988 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Modell, Sol (prof - Valley College) 1989, 01/03/1989-12/27/1989 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Modell, Sol (prof - Valley College) 1990, 01/02/1990-12/17/1990 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Modell, Sol (prof - Valley College) 1991-1993, 03/06/1991-11/14/1993 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Modell, Sol (prof - Valley College) 1994-1997, 02/20/1994-07/17/1997 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Morrisey, William 1979, 01/06/1979-12/28/1979 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Morrisey, William 1980-1981, 01/09/1980-12/23/1981 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Morrisey, William 1982-1983, 01/08/1982-10/09/1983 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Morrisey, William 1984-1988, 01/03/1984-12/26/1988 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Morrisey, William 1989-1994, 02/14/1989-06/18/1994 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Morrisey, William 1998-2002, 07/27/1998-04/02/2002 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Moskovitz, Irving (dr), 08/21/1980-04/23/1992 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - National Foundation for Jewish Culture, 03/01/1981-11/17/1981 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - National Jewish Coalition/National PAC - Brooks, Charles, 05/31/1985-05/11/2000 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Near-East Report, 07/17/1978-11/22/1993 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - New Israel Fund, 11/23/1987 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Nordau Circle of the Jabotinsky Fraternal Order Inc. - Taubenfeld, Sol, 12/04/1980-12/31/1982 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Options Publishing Company - Singer, Betty, 09/14/1980-07/28/1986 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Organizations, 1978-1995 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    [from contents page of folder:] Advanced International Studies Institute; American Association for Jewish Education; Americans for a Secure Israel; American Zionist Youth Foundation Inc.; Center for International Security; Center for International Studies; Committee for the economic growth of Israel; Conference of Presidents of Major Jewish Organizations; Council on Energy Policy; Foreign Policy Perspectives; Institute of Hebrew Unity; I.R.I.S.; Israel Public Policy Institute; Jerusalem Bible Institute; Jewish Agency American Section Inc; Jewish Exponent; Jewish National Fund; J.I.N.S.A.; National Jewish Resource Center; Republican National Committee; Torah Dept.; Veterans Judean Battalions Inc; Womens League for Conservative Judaism; YIVO Institute
  - Osdoba, Avi, 01/07/1985 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Outstanding Friends of Israel, 01/14/1993 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Perl, William (dr), 11/28/1980-05/21/1986 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Pisar, Samuel (attorney), 04/02/1981-05/14/1981 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Plaut, Steven (prof - Oberlin College), 09/30/1980-11/17/1980 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Pro Israel New York, 05/27/1994 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Rabin, Jack (dr), 03/10/1981-08/31/1989 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Reichel, Aaron esq., 03/16/1994-11/18/1997 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Ribenfeld, Paul (dr), 09/09/1980-10/06/1989 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Ringel, David, 02/10/1995-08/16/2000 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Ritman, Larry, 05/22/1978-04/30/1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Rothschild, David - Nefesh, the Jewish Soul, 02/1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Saidel, Raymond, 01/19/1979-05/01/1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)